necklace5 =[
  {"question":"骯髒","Answer":"āngzāng"},
  {"question":"及","Answer":"jí"},
  {"question":"衣服","Answer":"yīfú"},
  {"question":"乾燥","Answer":"gānzào"},
  {"question":"粗糙","Answer":"cūcāo"},
  {"question":"瑪蒂達","Answer":"mǎdì dá"},
  {"question":"貧窮","Answer":"pínqióng"},
  {"question":"節省","Answer":"jiéshěng"},
  {"question":"即使","Answer":"jíshǐ"},
  {"question":"挨 店主","Answer":"āi   diànzhǔ"},
  {"question":"討價","Answer":"tǎojià"},
  {"question":"刻","Answer":"kè"},
  {"question":"放鬆","Answer":"fàngsōng"},
  {"question":"兼職賺錢","Answer":"jiānzhí zhuànqián"},
  {"question":"持續","Answer":"chíxù"},
  {"question":"久","Answer":"jiǔ"},
  {"question":"辛苦及勞累","Answer":"xīnkǔ jí láolèi"},
  {"question":"還清","Answer":"huánqīng"},
  {"question":"債務","Answer":"zhàiwù"},
  {"question":"利息","Answer":"lìxī"},
  {"question":"當初","Answer":"dāngchū"},
  {"question":"遺失","Answer":"yíshī"},
  {"question":"艱苦","Answer":"jiānkǔ"},
  {"question":"難以預料","Answer":"nányǐyùliào"},
  {"question":"往往","Answer":"wǎngwǎng"},
  {"question":"不禁","Answer":"bùjīn"},
  {"question":"眼框","Answer":"yǎnkuàng"},
  {"question":"禮拜","Answer":"lǐbài"},
  {"question":"瑪蒂達","Answer":"mǎdì dá"},
  {"question":"既","Answer":"jì"},
  {"question":"美艷","Answer":"měiyàn"},
  {"question":"瞬間","Answer":"shùnjiān"},
  {"question":"貴婦","Answer":"guìfù"},
  {"question":"瑪蒂達","Answer":"mǎdì dá"},
  {"question":"心臟","Answer":"xīnzàng"},
  {"question":"禁不住","Answer":"jīnbuzhù"},
  {"question":"怦怦","Answer":"pēngpēng"},
  {"question":"債務","Answer":"zhàiwù"},
  {"question":"還清","Answer":"huánqīng"},
  {"question":"實話","Answer":"shíhuà"},
  {"question":"蒼老","Answer":"cānglǎo"},
  {"question":"瑪蒂達","Answer":"mǎdì dá"},
  {"question":"造成","Answer":"zàochéng"},
  {"question":"鑽石項鏈","Answer":"zuànshí xiàngliàn"},
  {"question":"嗯","Answer":"en"},
  {"question":"弄丟","Answer":"nòng diū"},
  {"question":"還給","Answer":"huángěi"},
  {"question":"項鏈","Answer":"xiàngliàn"},
  {"question":"款式","Answer":"kuǎnshi"},
  {"question":"訝異","Answer":"yàyì"},
  {"question":"瑪蒂","Answer":"mǎdì"},
  {"question":"自豪","Answer":"zìháo"},
  {"question":"值","Answer":"zhí"},
  ]